Muhammet Al ERŞEN

05466440893

muhammetaliersen@gmail.com

🚨 1238 / 2 sokak Ostim OSM mah.

Yenimahalle ANKARA

≝02/03/1995

A + B (Truckutbildning)

EDUCATION

Tobb Economics and Technology University 2014/2020

SKILLS

JAVA, JAVASCRIPT, REACTJS, APIS, REST, HTML, GIT, CSS, SQL, POSTGRESQL, MSSQL, JIR A, .NET, ANGULAR, SPRING, JPA & Hibernate, C/C++, SVN, DOCKER, BAMBOO.BITBUCKET.UNIT TEST, SONAR

LANGUAGES

English ★★★★ Spanish ★★

PROFILE

I graduated Computer Engineer and I have experiencein this field. I worked as a web developer and software developer for about 4 year. I had a lot of experience in web programming. I have improved myself in the main Java, javascirpt, C, Html languages. I can easily adapt to teamwork. I am constantly improving myself and my interest in new technologies is my most obvious ability. I can work full stack developer.

WORK EXPERIENCE

INTERN Software Engineer Zeg Teknoloji | 08/2018 - 12/2018

Frontend Backend devolopment User friendly interface design Team collaboration Angular

INTERN Software Engineer BİZNET BİLİŞİM | 08/2019 - 01/2020

Frontend Backend devolopment Creating Template Web page designing Team collaboration

Software Engineer LENORA BİLİŞİM | 09/2020- 08/2022

Frontend Backend devolopment Creating Template Web devolopment Webapi design

Software Engineer Bilişim AŞ | 08/2022 - 09/2023

Full Stack Developer Continuous integration Rest Api Implementation

Computer Engineer Infonal | 09/2023 - PRESENT

Reviewed code, debugged problems, and corrected issues. Used NodeJS, ORM and SQL/No-SQL to develop and manage databases. Worked with back-end developers to design APIs. Developed unit test cases for testing and automation.